The Surrender is a drama, horror film directed by Julia Max.
A fraught mother-daughter relationship is put to a terrifying test when the family patriarch dies, and
the grieving mother hires a mysterious stranger to bring her husband back from the dead.
Barbara, played by Kate Burton.
Megan, played by Colby Minifie.
The Man, played by Neil Sandilands.
Robert, played by Vaughn Armstrong.
Nikki, played by Mia Ellis.
Young Robert, played by Pete Ploszek.
Surrender is a 2025 Indian Tamil-language action thriller film written and directed by debutant Gowthaman Ganapathy, starring
Tharshan in the lead role alongside Lal, Sujith Shankar, Munishkanth, Padine Kumar and others in important roles.
Surrender released in theatres on 1 August 2025.
The tone is dark and emotional.